leveltrade.com 2015-12-31

# LevelTrade forex market broker

PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT OF 

Leveltarde Limited

The protection of privacy and the safeguarding of our Clients’ personal and financial information is our highest priority.

Please view the following Privacy Policy Statement which clearly explains how we, at Leveltarde Limited (here and after - Leveltarde), collect, process, store and protect our Clients’ information.

By opening an account, Client hereby consents to such collection, processing, storage and use of personal information by Leveltrade 

as explained below.

COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Leveltrade collects the necessary information required to open, transact and safeguard your assets and your privacy and to provide you with the services you require. To this end, Leveltrade gathers information from you and may, in certain circumstances, gather information from relevant banks and/or credit agencies, and/or other sources which help us profile your requirements and preferences and provide better services to you. 

The information Leveltrade collects may include: 

Application information 

Personal information you provide us in your application form, such as your name, address, date of birth, email address, income and income source etc. in order to facilitate the evaluation of your application. The information you provide us is also used for the 

purposes of communicating with you.

Transaction information 

Information about the anticipated volume and value of your transactions with us and income information provided in order to enable the construction of your economic profile.

Verification information 

Information necessary to verify your identity, such as an identification card, passport or driver’s license. This also includes background information we receive about you from public records or from other entities not affiliated with Leveltrade.

USAGE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION/OPT OUT

Leveltrade uses personal information only as required to provide quality service and security to you. This information helps improve services, customize browsing experience and enables us to inform you of additional products, services or promotions relevant to you and the products and services you require and you consent to us using this data for such purposes. 

If you do not want to receive information of this nature for any reason, please contact us at the following 

address:[support@leveltrade.com](mailto:support@leveltrade.com). 

Although you are not required to provide Leveltrade any of the personal information that we may request, please note that failure to do so could result in Leveltrade not being able to open your account or provide you with the service you require. 

Whilst we attempt to ensure that all the information we hold about you is current, accurate and complete, we urge you to immediately contact us if any of your personal details have changed. 

PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Any personal information you provide us will be treated as confidential and shared only within Leveltrade and will not be disclosed to any third party. 

The personal information that you provide in connection with registering yourself as a user of Leveltrade.com is protected in many ways. You can access your Registration Information through a password assigned to you. This password is encrypted and known only to you and shall not be revealed to anyone else. 

Registration Information is safely stored on secure servers that only authorised personnel have access to via password. Leveltrade encrypts all personal information as it is transferred to Leveltrade and thus makes all necessary effort to prevent unauthorised parties from viewing any such information. 

NON-AFFILIATED THIRD PARTIES

Leveltrade does not sell, license, lease or otherwise disclose personal information to third parties. 

Leveltrade reserves the right to disclose information as necessary to credit reporting or collection agencies as reasonably required in order to provide the services to you. 

To help us improve our services, Leveltrade may engage third parties to help carry out certain internal functions such as account processing, fulfillment, client service, client satisfaction surveys or other data collection activities relevant to our business. Use of the shared information may also be used to provide professional, legal, or accounting advice to Leveltrade. Use of shared information is strictly limited to the performance of the above and is not permitted for any other purpose. All third parties with which Leveltrade shares personal information are required to protect such personal information in accordance with all relevant legislation and in a manner similar to the way Leveltrade protects the same. Leveltrade will not share personal information with third parties which it considers will not afford its Clients the required level of protection

Where you have been introduced to us by a Business Introducer, such Business Introducer may have access to your information. You hereby unambiguously and unequivocally consent to the sharing of information with such Business Introducer. 

You acknowledge that in order to provide services to you, it may be necessary for information to be transferred outside of the European Economic Area and you consent to such transfer. 

USE OF "COOKIES"

Leveltrade uses cookies to secure your trading activities and to enhance the performance of the Markets.com website. Cookies used by Leveltrade do not contain personal information or other sensitive information. 

Leveltrade may share website usage statistics with reputable advertising companies and with its affiliated marketing companies. The information collected by the advertising company is not personally identifiable. 

To administer and improve the Markets.com website, Leveltrade may use third parties to track and analyze usage and statistical volume information. The third party may use cookies to track behavior and may set cookies on Leveltrade’s behalf. These cookies do 

not contain any personally identifiable information. 

PRIVACY STATEMENT UPDATES

From time to time, Leveltrade may update this Privacy Policy Statement. In the event Leveltrade materially changes this Privacy Policy Statement including how we collect, process or use your personal information, the revised Privacy Policy Statement will be posted on the website Client agrees to accept posting of a revised Privacy Policy Statement electronically on the website as actual notice to Client. Any dispute over our Privacy Policy Statement is subject to this Notice and our Terms and conditions agreement. Leveltrade encourages Client to periodically check back and review this policy so that Client always will know what information Leveltrade collects, how Leveltrade uses it, and to whom Leveltrade may disclose it. 

By clicking "I Agree" button I hereby confirm that I have read, understood and agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy Statement, and I confirm that I have full power and authority to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy Statement. 

For any other concern please [Contact Us](http://www.leveltrade.com/contacts)
